Finding Aid for the The Francis Robinson Collection
Special Collections and University Archives
- (The File Description)
  - Robinson Photograph Collection (Da - Fi)
    - Erede, Alberto (Box 82, Folder 79)
    - Escobar, "Home" (Box 82, Folder 80)
    - Etheridge, Dorothy (Box 82, Folder 81)
    - Evans, Edith (Box 82, Folder 82)
    - Evans, mary Jane and Albert (Box 82, Folder 83)
    - Evans, Maurice (Box 82, Folder 84)
    - Faieta, Eddy "Fay" (Box 82, Folder 85)
    - Fairbanks, Douglas, Jr. (Box 82, Folder 86)
    - Falstaff (Box 82, Folder 87)
    - Farrar, Elizabeth (Box 82, Folder 88)
    - Farrar, Geraldine (Box 82, Folder 89)
    - Farrell, Eileen (Box 82, Folder 90)
    - Farrell, Glenda (Box 82, Folder 91)
    - Faversham, Philip (Box 82, Folder 92)
    - Fealy, Mande (Box 82, Folder 93)
    - Ferguson, Gov. (Box 82, Folder 94)
    - Ferreira, Geraldo M. M. (Box 82, Folder 95)
    - Ferrer, Jose (Box 82, Folder 96)
    - Fetchit, Stepin (Box 82, Folder 97)
    - Field, Betty (Box 82, Folder 98)
    - Fields, William (Box 82, Folder 99)
    - Fields, W. C. (Box 82, Folder 100)
  - Robinson Photograph Collection (Fi - Ha)
    - Fitzgerald, Barry and O'Connor, Una (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Flagello, Ezio (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Flagstad, Kirsten (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Flemyng, Carmen, Bobby (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Fletcher, Bramwell (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Foley, Charles & Fritz, Kreisler (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Fontaine, Joan (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Fontanne, Lynn (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Forrestal, Michael (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Foster, Lillian (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - Fox, Stanley (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - Fracci, Carla (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - Francis, Kay & Rathbone, Basil (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - Franke, Paul (Box 83, Folder 14)
    - Franklin, Frederic (Box 83, Folder 15)
    - Frantz, Dalies (Box 83, Folder 16)
    - Fray, Jacques and Braggiotti, Mario (Box 83, Folder 17)
    - Frederick, Pauline (Box 83, Folder 18)
    - Fredericks, Shannon Leigh (Box 83, Folder 19)
    - Fremstad, Olive (Box 83, Folder 20)
    - French, Marilyn (Box 83, Folder 21)
    - Friedman, Erick (Box 83, Folder 22)
    - Friemann, Markus & Inka (Box 83, Folder 23)
    - Frohman, Mae (Box 83, Folder 24)
    - Furness, Thelma & Vanderbilt, Gloria (Box 83, Folder 25)
    - Gable, Clark & McLaglen, Victor, Meyer, Louis B. (Box 83, Folder 26)
    - Gabrilowitsch, Ossip (Box 83, Folder 27)
    - Gaite Parisienne (Box 83, Folder 28)
    - Galli-Curci, Amelita (Box 83, Folder 29)
    - Gallo, Fortune (Box 83, Folder 30)
    - Gambarelli, Maria (Box 83, Folder 31)
    - Ganz, Rudolph (Box 83, Folder 32)
    - Garbo, Greta (Box 83, Folder 33)
    - Garden, Mary (Box 83, Folder 34)
    - Garfield, John (Box 83, Folder 35)
    - Garris, John (Box 83, Folder 36)
    - Gaultney, John 0. (Box 83, Folder 37)
    - Gaynor, Janet (Box 83, Folder 38)
    - Gazzara, Ben (Box 83, Folder 39)
    - Gedda, Nicolai (Box 83, Folder 40)
    - Gentele, Marit (Funeral) (Box 83, Folder 41)
    - Gerard, Rolf (Box 83, Folder 42)
    - Gershwin, George (Box 83, Folder 43)
    - Geva, Tamara and Vilan, Demetrios (Box 83, Folder 44)
    - Giaiotti, Bunaldo (Box 83, Folder 45)
    - Gianinni, Dusolina (Box 83, Folder 46)
    - Gibbs, Vera (Box 83, Folder 47)
    - Gibson, Ian (Box 83, Folder 48)
    - Gielgud, John (Box 83, Folder 49)
    - Gigli, Beniamino (Box 83, Folder 50)
    - Gilbert, Ethel Bedient (Box 83, Folder 51)
    - La Gioconda (Box 83, Folder 52)
    - The Girl of the Limberlost (Box 83, Folder 53)
    - Gish, Lillian (Box 83, Folder 54)
    - Glenn, Wilfred (Box 83, Folder 55)
    - Gobbi, Tito (Box 83, Folder 56)
    - Goddard, Paulette (Box 83, Folder 57)
    - Goldovsky, Boris (Box 83, Folder 58)
    - Gorostiaga, Alberti di (Box 83, Folder 59)
    - Gorr, Rita (Box 83, Folder 60)
    - Graber, Betty (Box 83, Folder 61)
    - Grahame, Marept and McLaglen, Victor (Box 83, Folder 62)
    - Gramyer, Percy (Box 83, Folder 63)
    - Grand Ole Opry (W. S. M.) (Box 83, Folder 64)
    - Grapewin, Charley (Box 83, Folder 65)
    - Green, Martyn (Box 83, Folder 66)
    - Griffith, D. W. (Box 83, Folder 67)
    - Grigorieva, Tamara and Lichine, David (Box 83, Folder 68)
    - Grillo, Joann (Box 83, Folder 69)
    - Guarrera, Frank (Box 83, Folder 70)
    - Haas, Dolly (Box 83, Folder 71)
    - Hagen, Vta (Box 83, Folder 72)
    - Hagen, Walter (Box 83, Folder 73)
    - Hager, Anton and Davis (Box 83, Folder 74)
    - Hamilton, Edward K. (Box 83, Folder 75)
    - Hampden, Walter (Box 83, Folder 76)
    - Hampton, Hope, Wyatt, Robert and others (Box 83, Folder 77)
  - Robinson Photograph Collection (Ha - Ju)
    - Harding, Ann (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Hardwicke, Cedric (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Harold, Eleanor (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Harris, Family (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Harrison, Rox (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Harrison, Richard (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Harrison, Stanley (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Hart, William S. (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Harvuot, Clifford (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Hassell, George (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - Havoc, June (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - Hawks, Peggy & Scott (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - Hayes, Helen (Box 84, Folder 13)
    - Healy, Ted (Box 84, Folder 14)
    - The Heart of Salome (Box 84, Folder 15)
    - Heidelberg (Box 84, Folder 16)
    - Heifetz, Jaschua (Box 84, Folder 17)
    - Heller, Marina (Box 84, Folder 18)
    - Hempel, Frieda (Box 84, Folder 19)
    - Henderson, Dick Jr., Scott, Douglas & Wynyard, Dinna (Box 84, Folder 20)
    - Henderson, Ray (Box 84, Folder 21)
    - Henie, Sonja (Box 84, Folder 22)
    - Henry, Lolly & Douglas (Box 84, Folder 23)
    - Hepburn, Katharine (Box 84, Folder 24)
    - Herman, Bob (Box 84, Folder 25)
    - The Hermitage, Nashville, TN (Box 84, Folder 26)
    - Hersholt, Jean (Box 84, Folder 27)
    - Higerd, "Counsel" and Family (Box 84, Folder 28)
    - Higgenbotham, Lt. J. G. (Box 84, Folder 29)
    - Hill, Ann and George (Box 84, Folder 30)
    - Hines, Jerome (Box 84, Folder 31)
    - Hirano, Tadahiko (Box 84, Folder 32)
    - Hirth, Johanna (Box 84, Folder 33)
    - Hoctor, Harriet (Box 84, Folder 34)
    - Hoffman, Irwin and others (Box 84, Folder 35)
    - Hoffmann, Josef (Box 84, Folder 36)
    - Homer, Louise (Box 84, Folder 37)
    - Hopkins, Miriam (Box 84, Folder 38)
    - Horner Family (Box 84, Folder 39)
    - Horowitz, Richard and Family (Box 84, Folder 40)
    - Horowitz, Sonia (Box 84, Folder 41)
    - Hovick, Louise (Box 84, Folder 42)
    - Howard, Leslie (Box 84, Folder 43)
    - Howell, Mrs. Arthur (Box 84, Folder 444)
    - Hubermann, Bronislaw (Box 84, Folder 45)
    - Hume, William Family (Box 84, Folder 46)
    - Hurok, Sol (Box 84, Folder 47)
    - Huston, Walter (Box 84, Folder 48)
    - Huston, Walter (Box 84, Folder 49)
    - Ilitsch, Daniza (Box 84, Folder 50)
    - Ingram, Bronson Family (Box 84, Folder 51)
    - Iturbi, Jose and Iturbi, Amparo (Box 84, Folder 52)
    - Iturbi, Amparo (Box 84, Folder 53)
    - Jackson, Ethel (Box 84, Folder 54)
    - Jackson, Helen Frances (Box 84, Folder 55)
    - Jackson, Raylee (Box 84, Folder 56)
    - Janssen, Herbert (Box 84, Folder 57)
    - Jeans, Ursula with Lawton, Frank (Box 84, Folder 58)
    - Jenkins, Jane G. (Box 84, Folder 59)
    - Jepson, Helen (Box 84, Folder 60)
    - Jeritza, et al. with F. R. (Box 84, Folder 61)
    - Jeter, Sarah (Box 84, Folder 62)
    - Johnson, Edward (Box 84, Folder 63)
    - Johnson, Raymond (Box 84, Folder 64)
    - Johnston, Christine (Box 84, Folder 65)
    - Jolson, Al (Box 84, Folder 66)
    - Jones, John Price (Box 84, Folder 67)
    - Jones, Robert Edmund (Box 84, Folder 68)
    - Judge, Dick Family (Box 84, Folder 69)
  - Robinson Photograph Collection (Ka - Lu)
    - Kainz, Joset (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Kaye, Danny (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Kaye, Nora, Laing, Hugh, and Youskevistch, Igor (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Keith-Johnston, Colin (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Kelley, Gene (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Kelley, Pete (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Kelly, Emmet (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Kennddy, Arthur (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Kenndedy, Joan & F. R. (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Kerr, John (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Kibbee, Guy (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - Kiepura, Jan (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - Kilian, Hanns Family (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - Kimball, Oliver (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - Kipnis, Alexander (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - Kirsten, D. & F. R. (Box 85, Folder 16)
    - Kittrell, Hinton Family (Box 85, Folder 17)
    - Kollmar, Richard (Box 85, Folder 18)
    - Kozma, Lajos (Box 85, Folder 19)
    - Kreisler, Fritz (Box 85, Folder 20)
    - Kreutzberg, Harald (Box 85, Folder 21)
    - Kriza, John (Box 85, Folder 22)
    - Kullman, Charles (Box 85, Folder 23)
    - La Forge, Frank (Box 85, Folder 24)
    - Lagerwall, Mrs. A. G. (Box 85, Folder 25)
    - Laing, Hugh and markova, Alicia (Box 85, Folder 26)
    - Lamb, Christina (Box 85, Folder 27)
    - Lang, Gertrude (Box 85, Folder 28)
    - Lasses and Houcy (Box 85, Folder 29)
    - Laurel and Hardy (Box 85, Folder 30)
    - Laurier, Jay (Box 85, Folder 31)
    - Lauri-Volpi, Giacomo (Box 85, Folder 32)
    - Laughton, Charles (Box 85, Folder 33)
    - Lawrence, Gertrude (Box 85, Folder 34)
    - Lawrence, Marjorie & F. R. (Box 85, Folder 35)
    - Lawson, Nina (Box 85, Folder 36)
    - Lawton, Frank and Laye, Evelyn (Box 85, Folder 37)
    - Laye, Evelyn (Box 85, Folder 38)
    - Lederer, Francis (Box 85, Folder 39)
    - LeGallienne, Eva (Box 85, Folder 40)
    - Legit, Peter, and Lissi (Box 85, Folder 41)
    - Legruska, Ethel (Box 85, Folder 42)
    - Lehmann, Lotte (Box 85, Folder 43)
    - Leiber, Fritz (Box 85, Folder 44)
    - Leigh, Vivien (Box 85, Folder 45)
    - Leighton, Margaret (Box 85, Folder 46)
    - Leonard, Ada (Box 85, Folder 47)
    - Leontovich, Eugenie (Box 85, Folder 48)
    - Levian, Harry (Box 85, Folder 49)
    - Levine, James (Box 85, Folder 50)
    - Levitzki, Mischa (Box 85, Folder 51)
    - Lewis, William Mathew (Box 85, Folder 52)
    - Lhevinne (Box 85, Folder 53)
    - Littlie, Beatrice (Box 85, Folder 54)
    - Lincoln Center (Box 85, Folder 55)
    - List, Emanuel (Box 85, Folder 56)
    - Lloyd, George (Box 85, Folder 57)
    - Lloyd, Harold (Box 85, Folder 58)
    - Lohengrin (Box 85, Folder 59)
    - Lombard, Carole (Box 85, Folder 60)
    - Lombardi, Francis Family (Box 85, Folder 61)
    - London, George (Box 85, Folder 62)
    - Long, Huey P. (Box 85, Folder 63)
    - Longmire, Adele and Massey, Raymond (Box 85, Folder 64)
    - Lord, Pauline (Box 85, Folder 65)
    - Lorre, Peter (Box 85, Folder 66)
    - Louise, Anita (Box 85, Folder 67)
    - Lubitsch, Ernest (Box 85, Folder 68)
    - Lundburg, Bo (Box 85, Folder 69)
    - Lunt, Alfred (Box 85, Folder 70)
    - Luther, Hans (Box 85, Folder 71)
  - Robinson Photograph Collection (Ma - Me)
    - MaCarthur, Charles and Mary (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - MaCarthur, Jean (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Macbeth (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - McCormic, Mary (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - McCracken, James (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - McGee, Thomas, Jr. (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - McHugh, Frank (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - McLaglen, Victor (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - McLanahan Family (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - MacMahon, Mine (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - MacNeil, Cornell (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - Macready, George (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - Macurdy, John (Box 86, Folder 13)
    - Madeira, Jean (Box 86, Folder 14)
    - Manning, Richard (Box 86, Folder 15)
    - Manon (Box 86, Folder 16)
    - Mansfield, Richard (Box 86, Folder 17)
    - March, Fredric (Box 86, Folder 18)
    - Margo (Box 86, Folder 19)
    - Markevitch, Dimitry (Box 86, Folder 20)
    - Marlowe (Box 86, Folder 21)
    - Marlowe, Anthony (Box 86, Folder 22)
    - Marlowe, Bernia (Box 86, Folder 23)
    - Marsh, Calvin (Box 86, Folder 24)
    - Marsh, Larry and Penrce, Al (Box 86, Folder 25)
    - Martin, Lewis (Box 86, Folder 26)
    - Martin, Mary (Box 86, Folder 27)
    - Martinelli, Giovanni (Box 86, Folder 28)
    - Martini, Nino (Box 86, Folder 29)
    - Marvin, Jean (Box 86, Folder 30)
    - Mason, Edith (Box 86, Folder 31)
    - Massey, Ramond (Box 86, Folder 32)
    - Massey, Ramond; Abe Lincoln in Illinois (Box 86, Folder 33)
    - Matthews, Jessie (Box 86, Folder 34)
    - Media (Box 86, Folder 35)
    - Mehta, Zubin (Box 86, Folder 36)
    - Die Meistersinger (Box 86, Folder 37)
    - Mcichior, Lauritz (Box 86, Folder 38)
    - Melton, James (Box 86, Folder 39)
    - Menges, Herbert (Box 86, Folder 40)
    - Menken, Helen (Box 86, Folder 41)
    - Menotti, Gian Carlo (Box 86, Folder 42)
    - Menuhin, Yehudi (Box 86, Folder 43)
    - Meredith, Burgess (Box 86, Folder 44)
    - Meredith, Burgess (Box 86, Folder 45)
  - Robinson Photograph Collection (Me - Mu)
    - Merivale, Philip (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Merman, Ethel (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Merrill, Beth (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Merrill, Robert (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Old (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - New (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Chagall Morals for Metropolitan (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Metropolitan Opera Opening Nights (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Metropolitan Opera - general (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Meyer, Kerstin (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Middleton, Ray (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - Midsummer Night's Dream (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - Mielziner, Jo (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - Milanov, Zinka (Box 87, Folder 14)
    - Miller, Marilyn (Box 87, Folder 15)
    - Milnes, Sherrill and Family (Box 87, Folder 16)
    - Miraglia, Prospero (Box 87, Folder 17)
    - Mitropolous (Box 87, Folder 18)
    - Moffo, Anna (Box 87, Folder 19)
    - His Majesty Mohammed V, King of Morocco (Box 87, Folder 20)
    - Moissi, Alexander (Box 87, Folder 21)
    - Monte Carlo Opera House (Box 87, Folder 22)
    - Montgomery, Robert (Box 87, Folder 23)
    - Moore, Colleen (Box 87, Folder 24)
    - Moon, Charon and George (Box 87, Folder 25)
    - Moore, Grace (Box 87, Folder 26)
    - Moore, Grace (Box 87, Folder 27)
    - Moore, Grace (Box 87, Folder 28)
    - Mordkin, Mikhail (Box 87, Folder 29)
    - Morell, Barry (Box 87, Folder 30)
    - Morgan, Frank and Oliver, Edna May (Box 87, Folder 31)
    - Morgan, Helen (Box 87, Folder 32)
    - Morosova, Olga (Box 87, Folder 33)
    - Morris, Wayne (Box 87, Folder 34)
    - Lucy Banks Mower School of Dance (Box 87, Folder 35)
    - Muir, Jean (Box 87, Folder 36)
    - Muller, J. J. (Box 87, Folder 37)
    - Mumaw, Barton (Box 87, Folder 38)
    - Mundin, Herburt and O'Connor, Una (Box 87, Folder 39)
    - Muzio, Claudia (Box 87, Folder 40)
  - Robinson Photograph Collection (Mu - Pa)
    - Muni, Bella and Paul (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Muni, Paul (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Muni, Paul (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Munsel, Patrice (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Mustafa, Francis (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Nagy, Robert (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Natwick, Mildred (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Navoa, Salvador (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Nilsson, Birgit (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Nordin, Birgit (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - Norma (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - Novaes, Guiomar (Box 88, Folder 12)
    - Navarro, Ramon (Box 88, Folder 13)
    - Novotna, Jarmila (Box 88, Folder 14)
    - Oberon, Merk (Box 88, Folder 15)
    - The Old Harp Singer of Nashville, TN (Box 88, Folder 16)
    - Old Heidelberg Singer (Box 88, Folder 17)
    - Old Vic Theater Company (Box 88, Folder 18)
    - Oliver, Edna May (Box 88, Folder 19)
    - Oliver, Laurence (Box 88, Folder 20)
    - Oliver, Laurence (Box 88, Folder 21)
    - Oliver, Laurence (Box 88, Folder 22)
    - Ormandy, Eugene (Box 88, Folder 23)
    - Otello (Box 88, Folder 24)
    - Owens, Mr. and Mrs. Ralph (Box 88, Folder 25)
    - Paderewski, I. J. (Box 88, Folder 26)
    - Pagent, Christopher Anthony (Box 88, Folder 27)
    - Pagliacci (Box 88, Folder 28)
    - Palisi, Philip Michael (Box 88, Folder 29)
    - Palmer, Lili (Box 88, Folder 30)
  - Robinson Photograph Collection (Pa - Ro)
    - Pan, Hermes (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Panni, Nicoletta (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Parker, Fitzgerald (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Parker, Jean (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - The Parthenon, Nashville, TN (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Patterson, Elizabeth (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Patti, Adelina (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Pauly, Rose (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Pavarotti, Luciano (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Pavillon (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - Peardon, Patricia (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - Peik, Marna (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - Perlman, Itzhak (Box 89, Folder 13)
    - Perner, Hans (Box 89, Folder 14)
    - Perper, Kathleen and Leo (Box 89, Folder 15)
    - Peters, Roberta (Box 89, Folder 16)
    - Petina, Irra (Box 89, Folder 17)
    - Piatigorsky, Gregor (Box 89, Folder 18)
    - Pickford, Mary (Box 89, Folder 19)
    - Pinza, Ezio (Box 89, Folder 20)
    - Pitt, Clara (Box 89, Folder 21)
    - Pitts, Zazu (Box 89, Folder 22)
    - Platoff, Mare and Rostova, Lubor (Box 89, Folder 23)
    - Pons, Lily (Box 89, Folder 24)
    - Ponselle, Rosa (Box 89, Folder 25)
    - Porcelli, Aurelio A. (Box 89, Folder 26)
    - Power, Tyrone (Box 89, Folder 27)
    - Prandelli, Giacinto (Box 89, Folder 28)
    - Price, Leontyne (Box 89, Folder 29)
    - Robinoff, Max (Box 89, Folder 30)
    - Rachmaninoff, Serge (Box 89, Folder 31)
    - Rainer, Luise (Box 89, Folder 32)
    - Rand, Sally (Box 89, Folder 33)
    - Raquello, Edward (Box 89, Folder 34)
    - Raskin, Judith (Box 89, Folder 35)
    - Reardon, John (Box 89, Folder 36)
    - Redman, Joyce (Box 89, Folder 37)
    - Reid, Wallace (Box 89, Folder 38)
    - Rescigno (Box 89, Folder 39)
    - Resnik, Regina (Box 89, Folder 40)
    - Rethberg, Elizabeth (Box 89, Folder 41)
    - Rice, Keith and Joe (Box 89, Folder 42)
    - Ricci, Ruggiero (Box 89, Folder 43)
    - Riggan, Byron (Box 89, Folder 44)
    - Rigoletto (Box 89, Folder 45)
    - Richard, Cyril (Box 89, Folder 46)
    - Robeson, Paul (Box 89, Folder 47)
    - Robinson, Edward G. (Box 89, Folder 48)
  - Robinson Photograph Collection (Ro - Ry)
    - Robinson, Francis (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Robinson, Francis and Family (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Robinson, Francis and Others (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Robinson, Francis and Others (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Robson, Flora (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Rogers, Ginger (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Rogers, Will (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Rollins, Steve (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Romau, Vega and Dr. D. A. (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Romeo and Juliet (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Roosevelt, F. D. (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - Rorem, Ned (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - Rosario and Antonio (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - Rose, David (Box 90, Folder 14)
    - Der Rosenkavalier (Box 90, Folder 15)
    - Rosenstock, Juseph (Box 90, Folder 16)
    - Rosenthal, Moriz (Box 90, Folder 17)
    - Rothier, Leon (Box 90, Folder 18)
    - Rounseville, Robert (Box 90, Folder 19)
    - 20 Rubinoff, Dave (Box 90, Folder 20)
    - Ruffo, Titto (Box 90, Folder 21)
    - Ruhl, Eddy (Box 90, Folder 22)
    - Min Ryan's Home (Box 90, Folder 23)
  - Robinson Photograph Collection (Sa - Sp)
    - Stokowski, Samaroff Olga (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Sanchez, Joanne and Michael (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Santi, Nello (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Sayao, Bidu (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Scheherazads (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Schipa, Tito (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Schippers, Thomas (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Schmidt, I. W. (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Schmidt, Joseph (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Schumann-Heink, Ernestine (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Scott, Ivy (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Scott, Norman (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Scotto, Ranata (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - Scovotti, Jeanette (Box 91, Folder 14)
    - Segunda, Marin de Gloria (Box 91, Folder 15)
    - Seiler, Nadine (Box 91, Folder 16)
    - Sereni, Mario (Box 91, Folder 17)
    - Shabckvsky, Yurck (Box 91, Folder 18)
    - Shaw, George B. (Box 91, Folder 19)
    - Shawn, Ted (Box 91, Folder 20)
    - Shearer, Norma (Box 91, Folder 21)
    - Sherwood, Robert E. and others (Box 91, Folder 22)
    - Shields, Arthur (Box 91, Folder 23)
    - Shirai, Hirofumi (Box 91, Folder 24)
    - Shirley, George (Box 91, Folder 25)
    - Siegfried (Box 91, Folder 26)
    - Siepi, Cesare (Box 91, Folder 27)
    - Sills, Beverly (Box 91, Folder 28)
    - Siler, Charlie and Tommy (Box 91, Folder 29)
    - Skinner, Cornelia 0. (Box 91, Folder 30)
    - Sknczynski, Ruth (Box 91, Folder 31)
    - Slezak, Walter (Box 91, Folder 32)
    - Smith, Richard (Box 91, Folder 33)
    - Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs (Box 91, Folder 34)
    - Sokoloff, Vladimir (Box 91, Folder 35)
    - Solti, Georg (Box 91, Folder 36)
    - Sorantin, Erich (Box 91, Folder 37)
    - Sousa, John P. (Box 91, Folder 38)
    - Souvaine, Geraldine (Box 91, Folder 39)
    - Spalding, Albert (Box 91, Folder 40)
    - Phil Spitalny and All-Girl Singing Orchestra (Box 91, Folder 41)
    - Spoto, Bernadette & Frank (Box 91, Folder 42)
  - Robinson Photograph Collection (Sta - Stu)
    - Stahlman, James (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Stanwyck, Barbara (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Steber, Eleanor (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Stein, Gertude (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Stelle, Antoinette with F. R. (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Stevens, Rise (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Stewart, James (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Stokowski, Leopold (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Stone, Dorothy (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Stone, Thomas R. (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Strange, Michael (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Straus, T. & F. R. (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - Stuart, Lynne (Box 92, Folder 13)
    - "The Student Prince" (Box 92, Folder 14)
    - "The Student Prince" (Box 92, Folder 15)
    - "The Student Prince" (Box 92, Folder 16)
    - "The Student Prince" (Box 92, Folder 17)
    - "The Student Prince" (Box 92, Folder 18)
    - "The Student Prince" (Box 92, Folder 19)
    - "The Student Prince" (Box 92, Folder 20)
    - "The Student Prince" (Box 92, Folder 21)
    - "The Student Prince" (Box 92, Folder 22)
    - "The Student Prince" (Box 92, Folder 23)
    - "The Student Prince" (Box 92, Folder 24)
  - Robinson Photograph Collection (Stu - Tw)
    - Studholme, Marie (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Stueckgold, Grete (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Sullavan, Margaret (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Sutherland, Joan (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Swanson, Gloria and others (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Swarthout, Gladys (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Synge, J. M. (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Tagliavini, Ferruccio (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Talley, Marion (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Talmadge, Norma (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Talvela, Martti (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Tamagno, Francesco (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Taplin, Frank (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - Tapps, Georgie (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - Taylor, Lark (Box 93, Folder 15)
    - Taylor, Laurette (Box 93, Folder 16)
    - Taylor, Robert (Box 93, Folder 17)
    - Tchaldi, Renata (Box 93, Folder 18)
    - Tellegen, Lon (Box 93, Folder 19)
    - Temples, Shirley and Wertley, Helen (Box 93, Folder 20)
    - Terris, Norma with F. R. (Box 93, Folder 21)
    - Tezuka, Norialci (Box 93, Folder 22)
    - Theatre, Inc. (Box 93, Folder 23)
    - Thebom, Blanche & Francis (Box 93, Folder 24)
    - Thomas, Frankie, Jr. (Box 93, Folder 25)
    - Thomas, Jess (Box 93, Folder 26)
    - Thomas, John Charles (Box 93, Folder 27)
    - Thomas, Richard (Box 93, Folder 28)
    - Thompson, Hugh (Box 93, Folder 29)
    - Thorborg, Kerstin (Box 93, Folder 30)
    - Tibbett, Lawrence and others (Box 93, Folder 31)
    - Tietjen, Andrew and Andrea, Peter (Box 93, Folder 32)
    - Tilden, Bill (Box 93, Folder 33)
    - Tippit, Lillian W. S. (Box 93, Folder 34)
    - Tone, Franchot (Box 93, Folder 35)
    - Toscanini, Arturo (Box 93, Folder 36)
    - Tourel, Jennie (Box 93, Folder 37)
    - Tozzi, Giorgi (Box 93, Folder 38)
    - Tracy, Spencer and Katharine Hepburn (Box 93, Folder 39)
    - Trapp Family Singers (Box 93, Folder 40)
    - Traubel, Helen (Box 93, Folder 41)
    - Travel Pictures (Box 93, Folder 42)